<resources>
    <string name="app_name">mycandy</string>

    <!--登录页面 Login Page /找回密码页面 Retrieve Password Page/注册页面 Registration Page-->
    <string name="logo">Welcome To mycandy</string>
    <string name="user">Account</string>
    <string name="phoneOrEmail">Please Enter Your Phone Number/Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="enterPassword">Please Enter A 6-20 Digit Password</string>
    <string name="confirmPassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="enterPasswordAgain">Please Re-enter Your Password</string>
    <string name="forget"><u>Forgot Password</u></string>
    <string name="register"><u>Register</u></string>
    <string name="login">Log In</string>
    <string name="country">Country/Region</string>
    <string name="choseCountry">Please Select A Country/Region</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="verification">Verification Code</string>
    <string name="enterVerification">Please Enter Verification Code</string>
    <string name="newPassword">New Password</string>
    <string name="enterNewPassword">Please Enter A New Password</string>
    <string name="reset">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="registerTitle">Register</string>
    <string name="next">Next step</string>
    <string name="privacy">Agree<u>"User Agreement And Privacy Policy"</u></string>
    <string name="privacy1">User Agreement And Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy2">\t\t\tWe attach great importance to the privacy of our users and the protection of personal information. When you use our products and services, we may collect and use information about you. Our company hopes to through the 《Privacy Agreement》hereinafter referred to as "The Policy" to explain to you how and when our company collects, uses and saves this information.

\n\n\t\tWe hope that you carefully read and confirm that you fully understand the content of this policy before using our products and services.

\n\n\t\tYour personal information will never be used without your consent for purposes not specified in this policy.

\n\n\t\tPlease note that all personal information you provide when you use our products and services, we are authorized to collect, unless you delete or do not allow our collection through system settings. When you cancel your account, our company will stop using and delete your personal information.

\n\n1，The following is personal information you authorize us to collect:

\n\n\t\tPersonal information refers to all kinds of information recorded in electronic or other ways that can identify a person or reflect the activity of a person, either alone or in combination with other information.
The personal information involved in this policy includes: basic information (including personal name birthday, gender, personal phone number, email address); network identity information (including system account, IP address, and email address); contacts; personal common equipment information; personal location information; personal health information.



\n\n2，Our company may use the personal information collected in the process of providing services to you for the following purposes:

\n（1）To provide you with services owned by the product;

\n（2）When our company provides services, it is used for identity verification, customer service, security prevention, fraud monitoring, archiving and backup purposes to ensure the security of the products and services provided by our company to you;

\n（3）Help us design new services and improve our existing services

\n（4）Make our company know more about how you access and use our services, so as to respond to your personalized needs, such as language settings, location settings, personalized help and instructions, or to you and other users respond in other ways;

\n（5）Software certification or management software upgrade;

\n（6）Let you participate in surveys about our products and services.

\nIn order to allow you to have a better experience, improve our services or other uses you agree with, under the premise of complying with relevant laws and regulations, our company may use the information collected through a service to collect information or personalize way for other services of our company. For example, the information collected when you use one of our services may be used to provide you with specific content in another service or to show you non-generalized information about you. If our company provides corresponding options in related services, you can also authorize us to use the information provided and stored by this service for our other services.

\n\n3，Our company will not share your personal information with any company, organization and individual other than our company, except in the following cases:

\n\n（1）With your explicit consent and authorization in advance;

\n\n（2）Provided in accordance with applicable laws and regulations, legal procedures, mandatory administrative or judicial requirements;

\n\n（3）To the extent permitted by law, it is necessary to provide for the protection of our company, our affiliates or partners, the public interest, property or safety from damage;

\n\n（4） Only by sharing your information can we achieve the core functions of our products and services or provide the services you need;

\n\n（5）To handle your dispute or disputes with others at your request;

\n\n（6）Provided in accordance with the relevant agreement with you or other legal documents;

\n\n（7） For use in the public interest in compliance with laws and regulations.

\n\n4，How we jointly protect and store your personal information:

\n（1）We attach great importance to the security of personal information and take all reasonable and feasible data security technical measures to protect your personal information;

\n（2）While no Internet environment is 100% secure, we do our best to ensure and guarantee the security of any information you send to us. If our physical, technical or management protection facilities are damaged, resulting in unauthorized access, public disclosure, tampering, or destruction of information, resulting in damage to your legitimate rights and interests, our company will bear the corresponding legal responsibility.

\n（3）If you have any questions about the protection of your personal information, you can contact us through the contact information on our official website. If you find that your personal information is leaked, especially your personal information has been leaked, please contact us immediately so that we can take corresponding measures.



\n\n5，Use of our services by minors：

We recommend that minors encourage their parents or guardians to read this policy and recommend that minors seek the consent and guidance of their parents or guardians before submitting personal information.



\n\n5，Application scope of privacy policy

 This policy applies to all our services except certain specific services. These specific services will use specific privacy policies. Specific privacy policies for certain services will more specifically describe how we use your information in those services. The privacy policy for that particular service forms part of this policy. If there is any inconsistency between the privacy policy of the relevant specific service and this policy, the privacy policy of the specific service shall prevail。

\nplease note that this policy does not apply to:

\n（1）Information collected by third-party services (including all third-party websites) accessed through our services;

\n（2）Information collected by other companies or agencies that perform advertising services in our services;

\n（3）If you use an Apple device such as an iPhone or iPad, in order to calculate your exercise data, with your authorization, we will receive and send your exercise data from Apple\'s Healthkit. Our company will read your height, weight and gender data from Healthkit. At the same time, your steps, walking + running distance, active energy, riding distance and sleep analysis data generated by mycandy APP will be written into Apple Healthkit. Any data obtained through Healthkit will not be shared or sold to any third-party company, and our company will not use the information obtained from Healthkit for commercial purposes such as advertising and marketing.



\n\n7， Update

\n\n\t\tWe may update or amend the terms of this policy, and such amendments form part of this policy. If such amendments cause a substantial reduction in your rights under this policy, before the amendments take effect, we will notify you via a prominent location on the homepage or email you or otherwise. In this case, if you continue to use our services, you agree to be bound by this revised policy.</string>
    <string name="checkPrivacy">Please Confirm You’ve Read The User Agreement And Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="setPassword">Set Password</string>
    <string name="china">China</string>
    <string name="vistor">Visitors to login</string>

    <!--主页 Main Page-->
    <string name="healthy">Health</string>
    <string name="sport">Sport</string>
    <string name="mine">Mine</string>
    <string name="touchAgain">Press Again To Exit The Program</string>

    <!--健康页面 Health Page-->
    <string name="planStep">Target Steps%d</string>
    <string name="sleep">Sleep</string>
    <string name="heart">Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="blood">Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="bloodo">Blood Oxygen</string>
    <string name="animal">Temperature</string>
    <string name="ecg">ECG</string>
    <string name="check">View</string>
    <string name="perfect">Perfect</string>
    <string name="good">Good</string>
    <string name="bad">Bad</string>
    <string name="quick">Quick</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="hot">Fever</string>
    <string name="slow">Slow</string>
    <string name="higher">High</string>
    <string name="flat">Low</string>
    <string name="pull_to_refresh">Pull Down To Refresh</string>
    <string name="release_to_refresh">Refresh After Release</string>
    <string name="refreshing">Refreshing...</string>
    <string name="refresh_succeed">Refresh Successful</string>
    <string name="refresh_fail">Refresh Failed</string>


    <!--运动界面 Sports-->
    <string name="best">Best Sport Record</string>
    <string name="history">Historical Movement Record</string>
    <string name="track">Sport Information</string>
    <string name="speed">Speed</string>
    <string name="kcal">Consumed (kcal)</string>
    <string name="time">Time</string>
    <string name="heart_rate">Heart Rate(bpm)</string>
    <string name="cadence">Cadence</string>
    <string name="distance">Distance(</string>
    <string name="speedData">Average Speed</string>
    <string name="heart_rateData">Average Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="strideData">Average Cadence</string>
    <string name="distanceData">Distance</string>
    <string name="basket">Basketball</string>
    <string name="football">Football</string>
    <string name="pingpong">Table tennis</string>
    <string name="badminton">Badminton</string>
    <string name="mountain">Mountain</string>
    <string name="bike">Biking</string>
    <string name="swim">Swimming</string>
    <string name="walk">Walking</string>
    <string name="treadmill">Indoor Running</string>
    <string name="runWithout">Running</string>
    <string name="marathon">Marathon</string>
    <string name="sufing">Sufing</string>
    <string name="boat">Boating</string>
    <string name="altitude">Altitude</string>
    <string name="speedPerHour">SpeedPerHour</string>
    <string name="avarageAltitude">altitude</string>
    <string name="climb">Climbing</string>
    <string name="skii">Skii</string>
    <string name="golf">Golf</string>
    <string name="tipForPrivacy">Permission to illustrate</string>
    <string name="getPrivacy">During use, the application requires access to location permissions to record and calibrate motion tracks and distances</string>


    <!--我的页面 Mine-->
    <string name="device">Device</string>
    <string name="stepPlan">Step Goal</string>
    <string name="sleepPlan">Sleep Target</string>
    <string name="find">Finding Watch</string>
    <string name="notification">App Notification</string>
    <string name="blePhone">Bluetooth Call</string>
    <string name="blePhoto">Bluetooth Camera</string>
    <string name="unit">Unit</string>
    <string name="face">Watch Face</string>
    <string name="myDail">My Dial</string>
    <string name="seeDail">Preview</string>
    <string name="diyDail">DIY</string>
    <string name="diyDailing">Updating...</string>
    <string name="diyDailOK">Update Successful</string>
    <string name="diyDailError">Update failed,please try again</string>
    <string name="upDownBackground">Please upload a background picture</string>
    <string name="chooseClock">Please select a clock style</string>
    <string name="clock">Clock Style</string>
    <string name="background">Upload Pictures</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="logout">Sign out</string>
    <string name="me">Mine</string>
    <string name="set">Setting</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="tip">Tip</string>
    <string name="delete">Are You Sure You Want To Delete This Data？</string>
    <string name="logoutTip">Are You Sure You Want To Log Out？</string>
    <string name="sendOK">Sent Successfully</string>
    <string name="searchDevice">Search Device</string>
    <string name="noDevice">No Device Found</string>
    <string name="connected">Connected</string>
    <string name="disConnect">Not Connected</string>
    <string name="connectting">Connecting</string>
    <string name="syceError">Watch Is Not connected，Data Will Be Synced To The Watch The Next Time You Connect</string>
    <string name="unBind">Replace Device</string>
    <string name="unline">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="line">Connect The Watch</string>
    <string name="addDevice">Add Device</string>
    <string name="help">help</string>
    <string name="FAQ">FAQ</string>
    <string name="guide">User Guide</string>
    <string name="service">Keep app active</string>
    <string name="huawei">HUAWEI</string>
    <string name="oppo">oppo</string>
    <string name="vivo">vivo</string>
    <string name="lenovo">Lenovo</string>
    <string name="oneplus">onePlus</string>
    <string name="samsun">Samsun</string>
    <string name="mi">MI</string>
    <string name="meizu">MEIZU</string>
    <string name="serviceTip">In order to improve the stability of the watch connection, it is recommended that you make the following Settings:</string>
    <string name="saverBettery">Do not open (power saving mode) :</string>
    <string name="bettyContent">If the power-saving mode is turned on, it may cause problems such as unstable Bluetooth connection, abnormal movement trajectory and reduced power distance. It is recommended to turn off the power-saving mode while in use.</string>
    <string name="protect">Set the method of background protection::</string>
    <!--蓝牙通话界面 Bluetooth Call Interface-->
    <string name="step1">1.Pair watch With Mobile Phone</string>
    <string name="step2">2.Unmatch</string>
    <string name="str1">1)Enter Bluetooth Function In Watch\n2)Search For Bluetooth Devices-Select Phone Bluetooth name\n3)Pair With Your Phone To Make Bluetooth Calls With Your Watch</string>
    <string name="str2">Enter System Setting-Bluetooth-Paired Device, Find Device, Enter Click "Unpair", Unpair Successful。\n\nRemark: Watch Cannot Use Bluetooth Call Function After Unpairing</string>

    <!--引导页-->
    <string name="guideTitle1">Preparations before binding</string>
    <string name="guideTitle2">Search Devices</string>
    <string name="guideTitle3">Choose Device</string>
    <string name="guideTitle4">Bluetooth pairing</string>
    <string name="guide1">Make sure the bluetooth of both the phone and watch is enabled</string>
    <string name="guide2">Click the device bar in the "Mine" interface to enter the search device interface.</string>
    <string name="guide3">Select your watch according to the device name and LE Address in the watch information interface</string>
    <string name="guide4">The APP will pop up a Bluetooth pairing request, and the pairing will be completed after confirmation</string>
    <string name="jump">skip</string>
    <string name="startApp">Continue</string>

    <!--关于界面 About-->
    <string name="version">Current Version</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="feedback_hint">Your feedback/question</string>
    <string name="tooLong">Input is too long</string>
    <string name="empty">Field cannot be empty</string>
    <string name="send_success">Submitted successfully</string>

    <!--单位制式界面 Unit System Interface-->
    <string name="measureUnit">Unit Of Measure</string>
    <string name="tempUnit">Unit Of Temperature</string>
    <string name="metric">Metric</string>
    <string name="british">Imperial</string>

    <!--报告页面 Report Page-->
    <string name="stepReport">Step Report</string>
    <string name="sleepReport">Sleep Report</string>
    <string name="heartReport">Heart Rate Report</string>
    <string name="bloodPressureReport">Blood Pressure Report</string>
    <string name="bloodOxygenReport">Blood Oxygen Report</string>
    <string name="animalHeatReport">Temp Report</string>
    <string name="ecgReport">ECG Report</string>
    <string name="day">Day</string>
    <string name="week">Week</string>
    <string name="sun">Sun</string>
    <string name="mon">Mon</string>
    <string name="tues">Tue</string>
    <string name="wed">Wed</string>
    <string name="thus">Thu</string>
    <string name="fri">Fri</string>
    <string name="sta">Sat</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="year">Year</string>
    <string name="allStep">Total Steps</string>
    <string name="averageStep">Average Steps</string>
    <string name="allSleep">Total Sleep Time</string>
    <string name="averageSleep">Average Sleep Time</string>
    <string name="light">Light sleep</string>
    <string name="deep">Deep Sleep</string>
    <string name="averageHeart">Average Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="minHeart">Min.Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="maxHeart">Max.Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="averageSBP">Average Systolic Pressure</string>
    <string name="sbp">Systolic Pressure</string>
    <string name="averageDBP">Average Diastolic Pressure</string>
    <string name="dbp">Diastolic Pressure</string>
    <string name="averageSao">Average Blood Oxygen</string>
    <string name="averageTemp">Average  Temp</string>
    <string name="maxTemp">Max Temp</string>
    <string name="passRate">Compliance Rate</string>
    <string name="ecgTip">Measurement is only for reference, not as a Medical Certificate</string>
    <string name="noData">No Report</string>
    <string name="tomorrow">Available in the future</string>


    <!--用户信息页面 User Information Page-->
    <string name="userInfo">User Info</string>
    <string name="picture">Image</string>
    <string name="userName">Nickname</string>
    <string name="enterUserName">Please Enter Your Nickname</string>
    <string name="nameLong">Nicknames cannot exceed 12 characters</string>
    <string name="sex">Gender</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="height">Height</string>
    <string name="weight">Weight</string>
    <string name="birthday">Birthday</string>
    <string name="album">Photo Album</string>
    <string name="camera">Camera</string>


    <!--提示语 Notification-->
    <string name="tokenTimeOut">Login Expired, Please Log In Again</string>
    <string name="enterRightEmail">Please Enter The Correct Email Format</string>
    <string name="httpError">Network Response Timeout，Please Check The Network Connection</string>
    <string name="logging">Logging in...</string>
    <string name="waitting">Please Wait...</string>
    <string name="resetSuccess">Password Reset Succeeded</string>
    <string name="passwordUnSame">Enter The Wrong Password Twice</string>
    <string name="saved">Saved successfully</string>
    <string name="notificationlistener_prompt_title">Enable Notifications</string>
    <string name="notificationlistener_prompt_content">mycandy Needs To Forward Application Notifications To Remote Smart Devices. Press\"Confirm\"Enter Notification Page To Activate.</string>
    <string name="lostDevice">Device Is Not Connected</string>
    <string name="permissionErrorForCamare">Permission Failed, Can Not Turn On Camera Function</string>
    <string name="findPermission">Permission Failed，Will Not Be Able To Search The Device List</string>
    <string name="applyPermission">Request For Access</string>
    <string name="shareFailForPermission">Share Failed, Related Permissions Failed</string>
    <string name="permissionErrorForSMS">Permission Failed, Unable To Turn On SMS Notifications</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading...</string>
    <string name="privacyTip">Thank you for trusting and using mycandy.
\n\n We will help you to understand our collection, use and storage of your personal information and your relevant rights according to the User Privacy Agreement.
\n\n When you use the mycandy app, we will collect your device information, personal information (avatar, nickname, height, weight, exercise data) and other information. We need to get your camera permissions, photo album permissions to upload your app avatar:
\n\n When you use the mycandy application to run outdoors, upload, share and store exercise information, we need to obtain your location permissions and other purposes to record your running track.
\n\n You can access, modify, delete your personal information or manage your authorization in the relevant pages.
\n\n We use industry-leading security technology to protect your personal information.
\n\n When you click "OK", you agree to the terms of this Agreement.</string>
    <string name="crop_pic_failed">Image capture failed, please select JPG image!</string>
    <string name="visiter">Visiter mode does not support this feature</string>
    <string name="newVersion">A new APP version has been detected. Do you want to update it now?</string>

    <!--分享界面 Sharing Interface-->

    <!-- Scan & Connect -->
    <string name="connect_error">\\n\\n You can access, modify, delete your personal information or manage your authorization in the relevant pages.</string>


    <!-- applist & appstore -->
    <string name="launchfail">\\n\\n We use industry-leading security technology to protect your personal information.</string>

    <!-- SettingActivity -->
    <string name="sms_preference_title">SMS</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_title">Loading</string>
    <string name="progress_dialog_message">Please Wait&#8230;</string>

    <!-- SelectNotifiActivity -->


    <!-- Service -->
    <string name="missed_call">Missed Call</string>
    <string name="accessibility_description">Active notification service in your accessibility setting. This allows Bluetooth to push application notifications to remote device.</string>
    <string name="batterylow">Battery low</string>
    <string name="pleaseconnectcharger">The battery is getting low,Please connect charger, Capacity</string>

    <string name="operate_error">Failed</string>

    <!--固件升级-->
    <string name="trigger_failed_due_to_low_battery">The battery of watch is low. Please try it again after charging!</string>
    <string name="update_failed">Watch upgrade failed,Please try again later!</string>
    <string name="send_firmware_date_success">Succeed in data transmition!</string>
    <string name="new_version">It has been the latest version currently</string>
    <string name="downloading_fota">Firmware is being downloaded</string>
    <string name="read_send_fota_file">It is being prepared</string>
    <string name="sending_fota_file">The file is sent now</string>
    <string name="bt_disconnected_while_transfer">Bluetooth connection is broken!</string>
    <string name="download_succeed_via_bt">Send completed, please wait for upgrade!</string>
    <string name="updated_firmware">Update successfully!</string>
    <string name="warning_updating_text">In the upgrade, please wait for the upgrade to complete, or timeout (%1$d minutes)</string>
    <string name="checkGPS">It has been detected that the position switch of your mobile phone is not turned on. To ensure the normal operation of the application, please turn on the position switch.</string>
    <string name="training">Training run</string>
    <string name="heart_switch">Measure your heart rate regularly</string>
    <string name="runFinsh">Please confirm whether you want to end the current running exercise?</string>
    <string name="runShort">The running time or distance is too short for statistics.</string>
    <string name="started">Please start running first</string>
    <string name="touchAgain1">Press again to quit running</string>
    <string name="unlock">Slide right to unlock</string>
    <string name="startRun">Start</string>
    <string name="product">Please select the service you want to use</string>
    <string name="bodyFat">Smart body fat scale</string>
    <string name="watch">Bluetooth watch</string>
    <string name="both">both scale and watch</string>
    <string name="finishInfo">Please improve the user information</string>


    <!--体重秤-->
    <string name="body_fat">Body Fat</string>
    <string name="last7days">Last 7 Days</string>
    <string name="last30days">Last 30 Days</string>
    <string name="physicalAge">Body age</string>
    <string name="body_score">Body score</string>
    <string name="weightData">The weight data</string>
    <string name="otherData">Other data</string>
    <string name="idealWeight">Ideal body weight</string>
    <string name="fat_free_mass">Lean body mass</string>
    <string name="fat_mass">Fat weight</string>
    <string name="muscle_weight">Muscle weight</string>
    <string name="protein_weight">Protein weight</string>
    <string name="water_weight">Water weight</string>
    <string name="obesity_level">Obesity grade</string>
    <string name="visceral">Visceral fat grade</string>
    <string name="body_fat_rate">Rate of body fat</string>
    <string name="muscle_rate">Rate of muscle</string>
    <string name="protein_rate">Rate of protein</string>
    <string name="skeletal_rate">Rate of skeletal muscle</string>
    <string name="subcutaneous">Rate of subcutaneous fat</string>
    <string name="bone_mass">Bone mass</string>
    <string name="lean">lean</string>
    <string name="chubby">Overweight</string>
    <string name="obesity">Obesity</string>
    <string name="lack">Insufficient</string>
    <string name="standard">Standard</string>
    <string name="lighter">Lighter</string>
    <string name="slightly">Mild obesity</string>
    <string name="moderately">Moderate obesity</string>
    <string name="severe">Severe Obesity</string>
    <string name="enormously">Extremely obese</string>
    <string name="uptilted">Slightly higher</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="particularly">Severely high</string>
    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="recessive">Recessive obesity</string>
    <string name="overweight">Overweight type</string>
    <string name="sports_obesity">Sports obesity type</string>
    <string name="standard_type">Standard type</string>
    <string name="standard_sport">Standard sport type</string>
    <string name="lean_type">Lean type</string>
    <string name="lean_athletic">Lean and sporty type</string>
    <string name="sports_bodybuilding">Athletic bodybuilder type</string>
    <string name="lack_of_exercise">Lack of exercise type</string>
    <string name="new_body_fat_data">The new weight data has been generated. Do you want to cover the data of the current day?</string>
    <string name="permissionErrorForLocation">Permission Failed, Unable to obtain scale data</string>
    <string name="stating">It\'s ready to weighing</string>
    <string name="stated">Click Rescan</string>
    <string name="measurement">Measurement failure, please put the electronic scale on the ground, and barefoot measurement</string>
</resources>